{
    "あ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/あ-ひらがな.45983fbb26410a069e25.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "a",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ah\" in \"ah, I got it\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "あ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "a",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "い-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/い-ひらがな.d03abda84a805e8ec8bf.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "い",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "i",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Just like the letter \"e\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "い",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "i",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "う-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/う-ひらがな.f532017ab9250b9c516e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "う",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "u",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"u\" in \"Uber\" the company"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "う",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "u",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "え-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/え-ひらがな.8c77c5bb40fe377abeed.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "え",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "e",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"eh\" in \"eh, it's alright\" in a low tone"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "え",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "e",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/お-ひらがな.a1b903c28df7e809d4bb.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "お",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "o",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"o\" in \"old\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "お",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "o",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "青-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/青-単語.41a0fa16439ddf83e786.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あお",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Blue",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Blue",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あお",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あお",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "blue",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ao",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "愛-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/愛-単語.cc5cb31ec744373ff3bc.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Love",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Love",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "love",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "上-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/上-単語.120ae215c6743c7fd53c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "うえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Above",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Above",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "うえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "うえ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "above",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "on top",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "on top of",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ue",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "いい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いい-単語.abb137567d43b8b527cc.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "王-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/王-単語.210f3704f50503daa2ab.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "King",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "King",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "king",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "follow",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false,
              "whyNotLookingFor": "おう does have this meaning but we are looking for another. (Hint: it's a noun)"
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "to follow",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false,
              "whyNotLookingFor": "おう does have this meaning but we are looking for another. (Hint: it's a noun)"
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "言う-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To say",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To say",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to say",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "iu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "いいえ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いいえ-単語.a84cd741595619f56e0c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いいえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "No (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "No (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いいえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いいえ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "iie",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "no",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "no (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "家-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/家-単語.9c5924dd4e88c209a49f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "House",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いえ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "home",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "house",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ie",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "House/Home",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "絵-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/絵-単語.504a59545faa6d1a2461.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "え",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Painting",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Drawing/Painting",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "え",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "え",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "drawing",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "painting",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "e",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "おい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おい-単語.77db3cbfa9931c61f05e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hey",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hey",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hey",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nephew",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Although they use the same hiragana, in this question we are looking for the word that is an expression",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "か-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/か-ひらがな.2f034d65fc1f606ff436.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "か",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ka",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Very similar to the \"ka\" in the \"kaw kaw\" sound a crow makes"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "か",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ka",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "き-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/き-ひらがな.08fcdc297c1519a4b576.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "き",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ki",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like \"key\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "き",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ki",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "く-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/く-ひらがな.7eb15b5b807f803c00cf.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "く",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ku",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"coup\" in \"coup de grace\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "く",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ku",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "け-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/け-ひらがな.cc15ebbe1ce3c07792a4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "け",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ke",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it just like the \"ke\" in \"kettle\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "け",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ke",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "こ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/こ-ひらがな.6d28596daf0c22a16969.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ko",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "\n                        Similar to the 'co' sound in 'coat' and\n                        except with a softer 'k' noise.\n                    "
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "こ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ko",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "あか-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/あか-単語.92ecac1ba104dda4d3b7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あか",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Red",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Red",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あか",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あか",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "aka",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "red",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "あき-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/あき-単語.562382cd5f306dca7b27.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あき",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fall, Autumn",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fall, Autumn",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あき",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あき",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "aki",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fall",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "autumn",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "おおきい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おおきい-単語.18ff8d1fd1006304630f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おおきい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Big",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Big",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おおきい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おおきい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ookii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "big",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "いか-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いか-単語.996f2709374077c10373.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いか",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Squid",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Squid",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いか",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いか",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ika",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "squid",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かいけい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かいけい-単語.4dad5a40b9ec048b29d6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かいけい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Check (at the restaurant)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Check (restaurant)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かいけい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かいけい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaikei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "check",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "check (restaurant)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "check (at a restaurant)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "きく-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/きく-単語.652fe8598ddfd147e571.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To ask, To listen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To ask, To listen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kiku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to ask",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to listen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かく-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かく-単語.d274d492c39890b6cad3.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To write",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To write",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to write",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かこ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かこ-単語.e8f4889c19d53a9922a0.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かこ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "The past, Past",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "The past, past",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かこ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かこ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kako",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "past",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "the past",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かう-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かう-単語.e237c50a2046a1a7dfe7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To buy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To buy",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kau",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to buy",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かお-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かお-単語.49c277697083727be9ea.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かお",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Face",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Face",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かお",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かお",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kao",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "face",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "さ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/さ-ひらがな.ce730ead27653a42d9bf.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "sa",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"sa\" in \"saw\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "さ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sa",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "し-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/し-ひらがな.4f1443a98a81d364432c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "し",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "shi",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like \"she\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "し",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "shi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "す-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/す-ひらがな.b46d860cc9251976bdc6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "す",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "su",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"sou\" in \"good soup\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "す",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "su",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "せ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/せ-ひらがな.4d0255a8ff70e635d533.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "せ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "se",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"se\" in \"seven\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "せ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "se",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "そ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/そ-ひらがな.28b5f5cf445ca09e6f64.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "そ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "so",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like \"so\" in \"soldier\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "そ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "so",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "酒-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/酒-単語.67ef5c334cc063343037.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "(お)さけ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Alcohol, Sake",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Formality",
            "explanation": "The お is optional but can be added for politeness to make おさけ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Alcohol",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さけ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "おさけ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "(お)さけ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "alcohol",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "sake",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "今朝-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/今朝-単語.6ae0a401ec88db592400.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "けさ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "This morning",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "This Morning",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "けさ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "けさ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "morning",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "けさ has a similar meaning but does not exactly mean morning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kesa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "this morning",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "朝-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/朝-単語.f4788bdbc4c11ebda933.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あさ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Morning",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Morning",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あさ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あさ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "asa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "morning",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "足-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/足-単語.201e04e191237ff000cb.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Leg, Foot",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Foot, Leg",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あし",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ashi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "foot",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "leg",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "feet",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "legs",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "好き-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/好き-単語.b578a2dc5378d92f3421.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "すき",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Like (e.g I like food)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Like (e.g I like food)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "すき",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "すき",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "suki",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "like",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "to like",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "貸す-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/貸す-単語.2cdbf1f1e849bc2efd84.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かす",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To lend, To loan",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To lend, To loan",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かす",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かす",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to lend",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "to loan",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "うすい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/うすい-単語.27ce19e09082731db96e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "うすい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thin (For flat objects, e.g. thin like paper)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thin (For flat objects, e.g. thin like paper)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "うすい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "うすい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "usui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thin",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "thin (for flat objects, e.g. thin like paper)",
              "distanceToAllow": 10
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "すこし-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/すこし-単語.e5884a24d145792cbc1a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "すこし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "A little",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "A little",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "すこし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "すこし",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sukoshi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "a little",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "little bit",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "a little bit",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "おいしい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おいしい-単語.44233490221b10beb6ea.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おいしい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Delicious, Tasty, Good Tasting",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Formality Note",
            "explanation": "Can be used for formal and informal situations"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Delicious (formal and informal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "うまい",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true,
              "whyNotLookingFor": "While うまい does mean this, \n                        it is only used for informal situations."
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おいしい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おいしい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oishii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "delicious",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "good tasting",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "tastes good",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "yummy",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "tasty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "塩-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/塩-単語.160513b91e43bcf7ff2b.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しお",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Salt",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Salt",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しお",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しお",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shio",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "salt",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "た-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/た-ひらがな.1bb30a63d736ab22c522.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "た",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ta",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ta\" in \"taught\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "た",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ta",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ち-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ち-ひらがな.9e52cfa0636869b2c53f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ち",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "chi",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"chea\" in \"cheap\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "chi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "つ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/つ-ひらがな.d7d6530ad2b65e97f667.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "つ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "tsu",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"tsu\" in \"jiujitsu\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "つ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tsu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "て-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/て-ひらがな.0b8cfdffb01df9a10d54.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "て",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "te",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"te\" in \"tell\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "て",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "te",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "と-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/と-ひらがな.5a3490ad6cc9c5591e14.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "と",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "to",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like \"toe\" except with a softer 't'"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "と",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "口-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/口-単語.7e8445b26c950ff916ab.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mouth",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mouth",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuchi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mouth",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "小さい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/小さい-単語.63dd11bc8b243d33f947.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ちいさい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Small, Little, Tiny",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Small, Little, Tiny",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ちいさい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ちいさい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "chiisai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "small",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "little",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "tiny",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "高い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/高い-単語.3e2012e9db3e0df52637.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "たかい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Expensive, Tall, High",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Expensive, Tall, High",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "たかい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "たかい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "takai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "expensive",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "tall",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "high",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "机-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/机-単語.899873c6c90844d120ab.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "つくえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Desk",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Desk",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "つくえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "つくえ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tsukue",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "desk",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "手-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/手-単語.2fd7e5aee2b2e1bed037.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "て",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hand",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hand",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "て",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "て",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "te",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hand",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "遠い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/遠い-単語.97148ecd55f05f689b20.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "とおい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Far",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Far",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "とおい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "とおい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tooi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "far",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "近い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/近い-単語.64c8e6fc495aad1fb200.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ちかい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Close (distance), Near",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Close (distance), Near",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ちかい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ちかい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "chikai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "close",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "close (distance)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "near",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "時計-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "とけい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Clock",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Clock",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "とけい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "とけい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tokei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "明日-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/明日-単語.1ccd6f36c5cabfd6d72f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あした",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tomorrow",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tomorrow",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あした",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あした",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ashita",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tomorrow",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "な-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/な-ひらがな.6189cb081e13b6dfe3e2.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "な",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "na",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"na\" in \"naughty\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "な",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "na",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "に-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/に-ひらがな.6c8e2d589dc67848f15d.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "に",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ni",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"nea\" in \"neat\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "に",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ni",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぬ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぬ-ひらがな.35f0768dd406d43fa1be.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぬ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "nu",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ne\" in \"new\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぬ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ね-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ね-ひらがな.73fae18f5858ff0e7976.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ね",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ne",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ne\" in \"nest\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ね",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ne",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "の-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/の-ひらがな.fe8b6d58f9190cdf3ef4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "の",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "no",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"no\" in \"annoyed\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "の",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "no",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "お金-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/お金-単語.56806f483c78bf230e32.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おかね",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Money",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おかね",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "okane",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "money",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Money",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おかね",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "大人-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/大人-単語.5f849a9620b18704df78.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おとな",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Adult",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Adult",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おとな",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おとな",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "otona",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "adult",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "grown-up",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "何-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/何-単語.b420c3535e947e244f7d.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なに, なん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "What, What is it",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "What",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なに",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "なに",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nani",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "what",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "what is it",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "what/what is it",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "魚-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/魚-単語.b1399da43b1560a051bd.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さかな",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fish",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fish",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さかな",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さかな",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sakana",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fish",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "国-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/国-単語.d53c7e03c382425c0ca1.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くに",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Country",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Country",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くに",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くに",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuni",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "country",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "楽しい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/楽しい-単語.1ef23d6791eaab083d11.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "たのしい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fun",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fun",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "たのしい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "たのしい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tanoshii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fun",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "enjoyable",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "夏-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/夏-単語.9bea99a07be12446dba8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なつ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Summer",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Summer",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なつ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "なつ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "natsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "summer",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "犬-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/犬-単語.09a7182be4fc9cf0d718.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いぬ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Dog",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Dog",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いぬ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いぬ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "inu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "dog",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "肉-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "にく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Meat",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Meat",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "にく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "にく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "meat",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "niku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "昨日-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/昨日-単語.e6f684548f994bb67bb9.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きのう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Yesterday",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Yesterday",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きのう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きのう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kinou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "yesterday",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "は-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/は-ひらがな.1487a9640eeb8efbbeab.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "は",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ha",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ho\" in \"hot\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "は",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ha",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ひ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ひ-ひらがな.a1599a10a55b3a8b3c57.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ひ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "hi",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the word \"he\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ひ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ふ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ふ-ひらがな.a897c0f39caf7ab62c6e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "fu",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to \"fo\" in \"fool\" except with a lighter 'f' sound. Produced with lips in a circular shape"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ふ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "hu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "へ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/へ-ひらがな.13d18b2d51eeb315ed5c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "へ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "he",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"he\" in \"hello\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "へ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "he",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ほ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ほ-ひらがな.59ad6ee3fa6d282bdb29.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ほ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ho",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ho\" in \"hole\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ほ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ho",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "花-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/花-単語.8a6bd2efeb4b604d7204.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はな",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Flower",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Flower",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はな",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はな",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hana",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "flower",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "話す-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/話す-単語.71ff3f1447b8796d990f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はなす",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To talk",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To talk",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はなす",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はなす",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hanasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to talk",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "人-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/人-単語.a4591d772a3e8ba33cc6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ひと",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Person, People",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Person, People",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひと",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ひと",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hito",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "person",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "people",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "船-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/船-単語.d7742e4d42da8779737c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふね",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ship, Boat",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Boat",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふね",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふね",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fune",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "boat",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "ship",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "太い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/太い-単語.d382c66604f4f512464a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふとい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thick",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thick",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふとい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふとい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "futoi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thick",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "細い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/細い-単語.cf185f9df2805b876134.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ほそい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thin (For people or cylinder objects like a stick)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thin",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ほそい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ほそい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hosoi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thin",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "thin (for people or cylinder objects like a stick)",
              "distanceToAllow": 12
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "服-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/服-単語.ebb73dbe0197702ed723.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Clothes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Clothes",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fuku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "clothes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "日本-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/日本-単語.d62f18f9f083242bffd9.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "にほん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Japan",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Japan",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "にほん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "にほん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nihon",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Japan",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "星-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/星-単語.6775f4f40b0f09d4b9f2.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ほし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Star",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Star",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ほし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ほし",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hoshi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "star",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "普通-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/普通-単語.8d09ab2f6a6372ddc5b8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふつう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Normal",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Normal",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふつう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふつう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "futsuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "normal",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ま-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ま-ひらがな.a727bb57e45ba1f6cb84.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ま",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ma",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"mah\" sound in \"mommy\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ma",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "み-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/み-ひらがな.187ff86d9ec247ac1374.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "み",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "mi",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the word \"me\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "み",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "む-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/む-ひらがな.fc88e9b8770dc5727855.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "む",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "mu",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"mo\" in the \"moo\" sound a cow makes"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "む",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "め-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/め-ひらがな.b9dad4786c46e7faa9af.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "め",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "me",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"me\" in \"metal\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "め",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "me",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "も-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/も-ひらがな.4a7d6bf32f20ba25abdf.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "も",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "mo",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"mo\" sound in \"mower\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "も",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "今-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/今-単語.95f2e0951530565cca53.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Now",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Now",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ima",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "now",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "飲む-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "のむ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To drink",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To drink",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "のむ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "のむ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to drink",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nomu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "耳-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/耳-単語.49be9d5d4e7694adf331.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "みみ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ear",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "みみ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mimi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ear",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ear",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "みみ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "道-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/道-単語.2254d96158c01bbafa45.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "みち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Street, Road",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Street, Road",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "みち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "みち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "michi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "street",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "road",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "名前-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/名前-単語.a2323b10fb5f164cbac5.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なまえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Name",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Name",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なまえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "なまえ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "namae",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "name",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "店-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/店-単語.8c39ea5213b2852bf0b1.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "みせ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Shop, Store",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Shop",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "みせ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "みせ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mise",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "shop",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "store",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "海-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/海-単語.78fe46d85922fb00fc5f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "うみ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ocean, Sea",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Ocean",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "うみ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "うみ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "umi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ocean",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "sea",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "重い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/重い-単語.807efd9f888f43dcb7e8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おもい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Heavy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Heavy",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おもい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おもい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "omoi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "heavy",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "寒い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/寒い-単語.fb77cf160389c7bf2775.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さむい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Cold",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Cold",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さむい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さむい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "samui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "cold",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "頭-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/頭-単語.81a4606d4a7fe443fca7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あたま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Head",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Head",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あたま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あたま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "atama",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "head",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "や-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/や-ひらがな.79765c23c10cda35e842.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "や",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ya",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"ya\" sound in \"yacht\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "や",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ya",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゆ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ゆ-ひらがな.df569cb572ecffba8d84.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゆ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "yu",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the word \"you\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ゆ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "yu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "よ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/よ-ひらがな.99f304bcd7762427841e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "yo",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounce it like the \"Yo\" in \"Yo what is up\" with a softer \"y\" sound"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "よ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "yo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "わ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/わ-ひらがな.72844a807c84dee736fa.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "わ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "wa",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Same as the \"wa\" in \"want\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "わ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wa",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "を-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/を-ひらがな.2da46d79a7712179e36b.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "を",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "wo",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounced the same as the Hiragana お"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "を",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ん-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ん-ひらがな.7787f93f661e88b11c54.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ん",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "n",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounced like \"n\" part of \"no\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "n",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "安い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/安い-単語.970eb718c954a639ef50.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "やすい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Cheap",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Cheap",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "やすい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "やすい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yasui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "cheap",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "山-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/山-単語.d3a646a8843850f8f405.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "やま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mountain",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mountain",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "やま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "やま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yama",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mountain",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "強い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/強い-単語.28ca0e46150721498981.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "つよい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Strong",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Strong",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "つよい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "つよい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tsuyoi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "strong",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "速い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/速い-単語.17d941b9fa13f076d1ef.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はやい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fast",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fast",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はやい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はやい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hayai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fast",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "冬-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/冬-単語.2feb1ce20dba3259fbc9.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふゆ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Winter",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Winter",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふゆ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふゆ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fuyu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "winter",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "野菜-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "やさい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Vegetable",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Vegetable",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "やさい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "やさい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "vegetable",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yasai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "部屋-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/部屋-単語.5ee197ec19e2d9a45a8a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "へや",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Room",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Room",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "へや",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "へや",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "heya",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "room",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "先生-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/先生-単語.219d985ba6a8a19c6a69.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "せんせい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Teacher",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Teacher",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "せんせい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "せんせい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sensei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "teacher",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "天気-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/天気-単語.294a89fcb6de54a546bb.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "てんき",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Weather",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Weather",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "てんき",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "てんき",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tenki",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "weather",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "悪い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/悪い-単語.75f5e3003e2f21fa6dda.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "わるい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bad",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bad",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "わるい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "わるい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "warui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bad",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "本-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ほん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Book",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Book",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ほん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ほん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "book",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hon",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "可愛い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/可愛い-単語.afede7bc28c6517e483a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かわいい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Cute",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Cute",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かわいい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かわいい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kawaii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "cute",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "変-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/変-単語.2c65679b3ed0b95f5618.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "へん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Weird",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Weird",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "へん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "へん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hen",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "weird",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ら-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ら-ひらがな.ab26d7239155b45a9cbc.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ら",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ra",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to the \"rah\" sound found in the \"ro\" in \"rotten\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ら",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ra",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "り-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/り-ひらがな.0e9b8d4b69ba633c1b9b.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "り",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ri",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to the \"ri\" sound from the \"re\" in \"revenge\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "り",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ri",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "る-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/る-ひらがな.ffbe576531e948dde0fa.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "る",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ru",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to the \"ru\" sound found in the \"ro\" in \"room\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "る",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ru",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "れ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/れ-ひらがな.8c6b1b8926b242b4afac.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "れ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "re",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to the \"re\" in \"rental\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "れ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "re",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ろ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ろ-ひらがな.bd4fb2ab994db91e85b7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ろ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ro",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Similar to the \"ro\" in \"rope\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ろ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ro",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "空-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/空-単語.fbc3813973b2195cade7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "そら",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sky",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sky",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "そら",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "そら",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sora",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sky",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "見せる-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/見せる-単語.6c7670f24cef4f5697a2.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "みせる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To show (an object)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To show (an object)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "みせる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "みせる",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "miseru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to show",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to show (an object)",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "古い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/古い-単語.741e436d609ded0e4b88.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ふるい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Old",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Old",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふるい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ふるい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "furui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "old",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "車-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/車-単語.08cec625ca867905f17c.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くるま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Car",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Car",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くるま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くるま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuruma",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "car",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "開ける-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/開ける-単語.b914416c00de8a3bbddd.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あける",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To open",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To open",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あける",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あける",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "akeru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to open",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "広い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/広い-単語.088278803ae79164fe0f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ひろい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Spacious, Wide",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Spacious, Wide",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひろい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ひろい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hiroi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wide",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "spacious",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "色-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/色-単語.336c7ec6e034a2890f63.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いろ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Color",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Color",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いろ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いろ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "iro",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "color",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "新しい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/新しい-単語.02f0fe8ed4f043dfd036.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あたらしい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "New",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "New",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あたらしい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あたらしい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "atarashii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "new",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "夜-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/夜-単語.3cabd548ae63412fd8cd.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Night",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Night",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よる",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yoru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "night",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "理由-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/理由-単語.88099d8f35ba16cf8f54.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "りゆう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Reason",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Reason",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "りゆう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "りゆう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "riyuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "reason",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゃ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゃ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small や",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "きゃ -> kya, にゃ -> nya, ひゃ - hya, ぴゃ - pya"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "みゃ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mya",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "りゃ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "rya",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゅ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゅ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small ゆ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "きゅ -> kyu, にゅ -> nyu, ひゅ - hyu, ぴゅ - pyu"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "みゅん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "myun",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "しゅ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "shu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ょ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ょ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small よ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples",
            "explanation": "きょ -> kyo, にょ -> nyo, ひょ - hyo, ぴょ - pyo"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "きょ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "kyo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "びょ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "byo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "っ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "っ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small つ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Emphasis the sound that comes after the small つ"
          },
          {
            "header": "Examples",
            "explanation": "かっぱ -> kappa, はって -> hatte, ぶっけ -> kakke"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "らっく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "rakku",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "だっき",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "dakki",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "が-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/が-ひらがな.703b8c88777b6419cff9.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "が",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ga",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "が",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ga",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぎ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぎ-ひらがな.e5184e12b7b450b62170.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぎ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "gi",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぎ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "gi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぐ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぐ-ひらがな.9797a8138d7faefcaf35.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぐ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "gu",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぐ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "gu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "げ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/げ-ひらがな.ff8215ee538684b362a9.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "げ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ge",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "げ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ge",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ご-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ご-ひらがな.8e7a5e49d8fb74965217.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ご",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "go",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ご",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "go",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ざ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ざ-ひらがな.b3a15f3284342ba23b30.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ざ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "za",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ざ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "za",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "じ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/じ-ひらがな.18b535c86382f6dbbd3e.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ji",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "じ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ji",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ず-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ず-ひらがな.a83f5b984ba1ddb386d8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ず",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "zu",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ず",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "zu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぜ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぜ-ひらがな.a10770935ff4f890fb33.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぜ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ze",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぜ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ze",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぞ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぞ-ひらがな.2a3a166578b4358bd9e3.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぞ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "zo",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぞ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "zo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "だ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/だ-ひらがな.14febb889f6f394ae276.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "da",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "だ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "da",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぢ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぢ-ひらがな.af05e9360a02c43c53fd.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぢ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "di",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounced the same as じ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぢ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "di",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "づ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/づ-ひらがな.a006595f23ba3676ee2f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "づ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "du",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "Pronounced the same as ず"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "づ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "du",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "で-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/で-ひらがな.2dc5a9e4c885622c9515.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "で",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "de",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "で",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "de",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ど-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ど-ひらがな.be282951270cdacdabe8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ど",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "do",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ど",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "do",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ば-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ば-ひらがな.1f265cf9505d044f3c26.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ば",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "ba",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ば",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ba",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "び-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/び-ひらがな.4a75749c87c6c143e330.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "び",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "bi",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "び",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぶ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぶ-ひらがな.122cac30ab6d2aa5e272.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぶ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "bu",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぶ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "べ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/べ-ひらがな.5b24158edbdc0b72505f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "べ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "be",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "べ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "be",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぼ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぼ-ひらがな.0783905ea102ef6d17c7.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぼ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "bo",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぼ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぱ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぱ-ひらがな.955b95617218f51c6342.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぱ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "pa",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぱ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pa",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぴ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぴ-ひらがな.829294668319aff9c8c1.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぴ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "pi",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぴ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぷ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぷ-ひらがな.b6722c9b0e1c3b606dcd.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぷ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "pu",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぷ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぺ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぺ-ひらがな.46cd08fce32af017398a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぺ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "pe",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぺ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pe",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぽ-ひらがな": {
      "conceptType": "Hiragana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ぽ-ひらがな.f11db7df66b2d201f79d.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぽ",
        "explanationHeader": "Romaji",
        "explanation": "po",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ぽ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "po",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "おはよう-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おはよう-単語.f8aa45076bf8e6619036.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おはよう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Morning (casual)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Morning (casual)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おはよう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おはよう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ohayou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good morning",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "good morning (casual)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "おはようございます-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おはようございます-単語.4df70ceae85c038bf995.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おはようございます",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Morning (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Morning (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おはようございます",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おはようございます",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ohayougozaimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good morning",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "Good Morning (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "こんにちは-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/こんにちは-単語.9ab18adae1e38e28a7fe.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こんにちは",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Afternoon",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Tip",
            "explanation": "The は in this word is actually pronounced as わ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Afternoon",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こんにちは",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "こんにちは",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "konnichiha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good afternoon",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "こんばんは-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/こんばんは-単語.0f9cf809003cce4b9965.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こんばんは",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Evening",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Evening",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こんばんは",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "こんばんは",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "konbanha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Good Evening",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "さようなら-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/さようなら-単語.1f3c759dc6d97e4b36f4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さようなら",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Goodbye",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Goodbye",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さようなら",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さようなら",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bye",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "さようなら has a stronger meaning implying that you won't see them again for a while and \"bye\" is a bit too light",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sayounara",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "goodbye",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "おやすみなさい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/おやすみなさい-単語.40b78a1f52fb87933139.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おやすみなさい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Night (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Night (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おやすみなさい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おやすみなさい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oyasuminasai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good night",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ありがとう-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ありがとう-単語.7201ab9fc9f93cbb42f6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ありがとう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thank You (casual)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thank You (casual)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ありがとう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ありがとう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "arigatou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Thank You",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "Thank You (casual)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ありがとうございます-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ありがとうございます-単語.714189ea1f10b1d0d935.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ありがとうございます",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thank You (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thank You (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ありがとうございます",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ありがとうございます",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "arigatougozaimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thank you",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "thank you (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "すみません-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/すみません-単語.00973332092c6f319d7f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "すみません",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Excuse Me, Pardon Me",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Excuse Me, Pardon Me",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "すみません",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "すみません",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sumimasen",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "excuse me",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "pardon me",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "いってきます-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いってきます-単語.9f19bf998c558ca873a1.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いってきます",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "See you later (When leaving home)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Only say this when leaving the house for work, school etc."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "See you later (When leaving home)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いってきます",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いってきます",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ittekimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "see you later",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "see you later (when leaving home)",
              "distanceToAllow": 8
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "いってらっしゃい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いってらっしゃい-単語.f2dd0b500f7dab538956.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いってらっしゃい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Have a Good Day",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Only say in response to いってきます"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Have a Good Day",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いってらっしゃい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いってらっしゃい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "itterasshai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "have a good day",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ただいま-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ただいま-単語.ccb26f9ccb67debcd7df.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ただいま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I'm home, I'm back",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Only say when coming back home from school, work, etc."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I'm home, I'm back",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ただいま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ただいま",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tadaima",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "i'm home",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "i'm back",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "im home",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "im back",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "お帰りなさい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/お帰りなさい-単語.34427eaa4ddf70e365d5.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おかえりなさい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Welcome Home",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Only say when a family member has returned home from school or work"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Welcome Home",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おかえりなさい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おかえりなさい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "okaerinasai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "welcome home",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "いただきます-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/いただきます-単語.eccecec6ba82fa79b699.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いただきます",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thank you for the meal (Before Eating)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Culture Note",
            "explanation": "This is said to express gratitude\n                    towards the sacrifices it took for you to receive\n                    your food. For example, the sacrifice of an animal or plants life."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thank you for the meal (Before Eating)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いただきます",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いただきます",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "itadakimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thank you for the meal",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "thank you for the meal (before eating)",
              "distanceToAllow": 10
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ごちそうさまでした-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/ごちそうさまでした-単語.e986cebecfe6963791e5.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ごちそうさまでした",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thank you for the meal (After Eating)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thank you for the meal (After Eating)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごちそうさまでした",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごちそうさまでした",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gochisousamadeshita",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thank you for the meal",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "thank you for the meal (after eating)",
              "distanceToAllow": 9
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "はじめまして-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/はじめまして-単語.ddb56bd8dabeb51b8827.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はじめまして",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I am glad to meet you (formal)​",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Often the very first word you say when you meet someone in a formal situation"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I am glad to meet you​ (formal)​",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はじめまして",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はじめまして",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hajimemashite",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "i am glad to meet you​",
              "distanceToAllow": 8
            },
            {
              "answer": "I am glad to meet you​ (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 11
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "よろしくおねがいします-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/よろしくおねがいします-単語.b490ab3e9f70cd03d27d.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よろしくおねがいします",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I look forward to working with you (formal)​",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Often the second word you say when you meet someone in a formal situation after はじめまして"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I look forward to working with you (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よろしくおねがいします",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よろしくおねがいします",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yoroshikuonegaishimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "i look forward to working with you",
              "distanceToAllow": 9
            },
            {
              "answer": "i look forward to working with you (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 11
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "はい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/はい-単語.c54652ec8b844a43f63d.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Yes (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Yes (formal)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "yes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "yes (formal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "うん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "うん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Yes (informal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Yes (informal)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "うん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "うん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "yes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "yes (informal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "un",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ううん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ううん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "No (Informal)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "No (Informal)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ううん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ううん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "no",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "no (informal)",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "uun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "一-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/一-単語.6a4265b5962e7a4e4afc.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "One",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ichi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "one",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "1",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "One",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "二-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/二-単語.79b236582ccbf6a5f54f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "に",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Two",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Two",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "に",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "に",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ni",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "two",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "2",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "三-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/三-単語.e11a1c601e4ad4962d73.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Three",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Three",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "san",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "three",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "3",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "四-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/四-単語.c8fd46ff16ab535754d2.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よん, し",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Four",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Four",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "し",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よん, し",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yon, shi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "four",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "4",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "五-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/五-単語.0c748a9f609bdc799ba8.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ご",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Five",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Five",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ご",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ご",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "go",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "five",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "5",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "六-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/六-単語.1fe77a18458934585ef6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ろく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Six",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Six",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ろく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ろく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "roku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "six",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "6",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "七-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/七-単語.9dc21ead8cc349d20eed.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なな, しち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Seven",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Seven",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なな",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "しち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "なな, しち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nana, shichi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "seven",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "7",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "八-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/八-単語.e50a5daab6536dcd8f88.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Eight",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Eight",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hachi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eight",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "8",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "九-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/九-単語.209a0450cde5b958c75f.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Nine",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Nine",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kyuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nine",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "9",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十-単語.b6782e6deafaf6877463.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ten",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Ten",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ten",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "10",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十一-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十一-単語.13326a84df80edd81272.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅういち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Eleven",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Eleven",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅういち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅういち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juuichi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eleven",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "11",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十二-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十二-単語.b294e31d01b29f21e2ca.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうに",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Twelve",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Twelve",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうに",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうに",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juuni",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "twelve",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "12",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十三-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十三-単語.03fb9868058622ec9353.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうさん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thirteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thirteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうさん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうさん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juusan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thirteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "13",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十四-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十四-単語.7aeda7d95b07a4691967.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうよん, じゅうし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fourteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fourteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうよん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "じゅうし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうよん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juuyon",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fourteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "14",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十五-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十五-単語.52d3faba0fa6279db8d3.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうご",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fifteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fifteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうご",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうご",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juugo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fifteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "15",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十六-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十六-単語.10d6a5815d5503b2d4ce.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうろく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sixteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sixteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうろく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうろく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juuroku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sixteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "16",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十七-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十七-単語.ad7202058eadb7ef52d4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうなな, じゅうしち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Seventeen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Seventeen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうなな",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "じゅうしち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうなな",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juunana",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "seventeen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "17",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十八-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十八-単語.2a5062e26e6b127530bb.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうはち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Eighteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Eighteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうはち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうはち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juuhachi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eighteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "18",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "十九-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/十九-単語.d29a9f59f637290376de.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅうきゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Nineteen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Nineteen",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうきゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうきゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juukyuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nineteen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "19",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "二十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/二十-単語.e93ca9f307f5530d7d82.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "にじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Twenty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Twenty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "にじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "にじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nijuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "twenty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "20",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "三十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/三十-単語.4c449a6e4f3156971017.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さんじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thirty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thirty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さんじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さんじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sanjuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thirty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "30",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "四十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/四十-単語.9c2829f4a4659a91d928.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よんじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Forty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Forty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よんじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よんじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yonjuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "forty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "40",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "五十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/五十-単語.5ea9f3cf40296ea931f4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ごじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fifty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fifty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gojuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fifty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "50",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "六十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/六十-単語.a686897444d047fddf8b.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ろくじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sixty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sixty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ろくじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ろくじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "rokujuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sixty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "60",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "七十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/七十-単語.7266198d0969805a4f7a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ななじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Seventy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Seventy",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ななじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ななじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nanajuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "seventy",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "70",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "八十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/八十-単語.0f1c9666135a9fa9ebcf.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はちじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Eighty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Eighty",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はちじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はちじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hachijuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eighty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "80",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "九十-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/九十-単語.6cca379132f557f0790a.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きゅうじゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ninety",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Ninety",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きゅうじゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きゅうじゅう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kyuujuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ninety",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "90",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "百-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/百-単語.3eb01200472ea6d39017.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ひゃく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hundred",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hundred",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひゃく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ひゃく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hyaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hundred",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "100",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "会社-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/会社-単語.baba1eae16f668c368e6.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かいしゃ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Company",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Company",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かいしゃ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かいしゃ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaisha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "company",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "学校-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/学校-単語.d32b207c455f861dfd35.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "がっこう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "School",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "School",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "がっこう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "がっこう",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gakkou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "school",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "かっこいい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/かっこいい-単語.ca818def071c8f480aed.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かっこいい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Good Looking, Cool",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Good Looking, Cool",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かっこいい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かっこいい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kakkoii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "good looking",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "cool",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "英語-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/英語-単語.64653948c1dc5b8faa93.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "えいご",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "English",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "English",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "えいご",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "えいご",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "eigo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "english",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "医者-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いしゃ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Doctor, Physician",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Doctor, Physician",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いしゃ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いしゃ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "doctor",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "physician",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "isha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "図書館-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "としょかん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Library",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Library",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "としょかん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "としょかん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "library",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "toshokan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "高校生-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/高校生-単語.14d16eb469265b9b0754.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こうこうせい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "High School Student",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "High School Student",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こうこうせい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "こうこうせい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "koukousei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "high school student",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "宿題-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/宿題-単語.8dd113a2db12d3f96555.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しゅくだい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Homework",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Homework",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しゅくだい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しゅくだい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shukudai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "homework",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "両親-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/両親-単語.fb3fb71f90837ab17c17.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "りょうしん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Parents (both)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Parents (both)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "りょうしん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "りょうしん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ryoushin",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "parents",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "parents (both)",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "午前-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/午前-単語.8355d1dc77ef457a76f4.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ごぜん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "a.m. (time)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Opposite from English, you say ごぜん before the actual time"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "a.m. (time)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごぜん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごぜん",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gozen",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "a.m.",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "am",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "午後-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/午後-単語.bf6fa6d76da244ed4172.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ごご",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "p.m. (time)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "Opposite from English, you say ごご before the actual time"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "p.m. (time)",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごご",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごご",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gogo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "p.m.",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "pm",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "友達-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/友達-単語.0a80312b80850e31d13b.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ともだち",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Friend",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Friend",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ともだち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ともだち",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tomodachi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "friend",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "仕事-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/仕事-単語.3822bc3e8575c1583d87.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しごと",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Job",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Job",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しごと",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しごと",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shigoto",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "job",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "主婦-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しゅふ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Housewife, Househusband",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note on Kanji",
            "explanation": "The word for housewife and househusband use the same hiragana but different kanji"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Housewife, Househusband",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しゅふ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しゅふ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "housewife",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "househusband",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shufu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "そうです-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/そうです-単語.5a4a4b86c12589146642.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "そうです",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That is Right, That is So",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "That is Right, That is So",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "そうです",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "そうです",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "soudesu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "that is right",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "that is so",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "大学-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/大学-単語.3760c16a3ebb4b517ca0.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だいがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "University, College",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "University, College",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "だいがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "だいがく",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "daigaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "university",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "college",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "私-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/私-単語.0e2aa86fc544eae75335.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "わたし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I, Me",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I, Me",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "わたし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "わたし",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "watashi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "i",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "me",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "学生-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "pronunciationFile": "/static/media/学生-単語.06d8a6cc18498a915781.mp3",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "がくせい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "School Student",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "School Student",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "がくせい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "がくせい",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gakusei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "school student",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "student",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "X は Y です-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "X は Y です",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "は marks the subject of the sentence and です is the formal way to end a statement.",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "ともだちはいしゃです。(My friend is a doctor) -> ともだち is the subject and the statement is the いしゃです part"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 2",
            "explanation": "いぬはかわいいです。(Dogs are cute) -> いぬ is the subject and the statement is the かわいいです part"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "わたし",
            "",
            "がくせい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "は",
            "です"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The は particle is needed to indicate that わたし is\n                the subject of the sentence and です is needed\n                to complete the statement of being a がくせい\n                in a formal sentence.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "I "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "am"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a school student. (Formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "ともだち",
            "",
            "しゅふ",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "は",
            "です"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The は particle is needed to indicate that ともだち is\n                the subject of the sentence and です is needed\n                to complete the statement of being a しゅふ\n                in a formal sentence.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "My friend "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a housewife. (Formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "さかな",
            "",
            "おいしい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "は",
            "です"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The は particle is needed to indicate that さかな is\n                the subject of the sentence and です is needed\n                to complete the statement of being おいしい\n                in a formal sentence.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Fish "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " delicious. (Formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "りょうしん",
            "",
            "せんせい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "は",
            "です"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The は particle is needed to indicate that りょうしん is\n                the subject of the sentence and です is needed\n                to complete the statement of being a せんせい\n                in a formal sentence.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "My parents "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "are"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " teachers. (Formal)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "の Particle Possessive-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "の Particle Indicating Possession",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "\n            One use of the の particle is to\n            indicate that one entity owns another\n            in the format XのY. Can sometimes be\n            interchangeable with the の particle to\n            connect nouns",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "にほんのやま (Japan's mountains) -> Japan possesses the mountains"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 2",
            "explanation": "だいがくのとしょかんのほん (The college's library's book) -> The college possesses the library which possesses the book"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "そら",
            "",
            "いろ"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to express the concept of a そら possessed by the いろ\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The sky "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "'s"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " color"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "わたし",
            "",
            "ともだち",
            "",
            "いしゃ"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の",
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to express the idea of not just anybodies friend but your friend and\n                that you are not just talking about any doctor but your friend's doctor\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "My"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " friend "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "'s"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " doctor"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "わたし",
            "",
            "いぬ"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to express the concept of a いぬ possessed by you (わたし)\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "My "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "dog"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "の Particle Connecting Nouns-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "の Particle For Connecting Nouns",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "\n            One use of the の particle is to connect\n            two nouns into one. Can even be used to\n            connect more if you use more の particles.\n            Can sometimes be interchangeable with the\n            の particle for possession\n            ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "いまのわたし (The current me)"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 2",
            "explanation": "にほんのふねのみせ (The Japanese boat shop)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "がっこう",
            "",
            "せいと"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to connect the nouns \"school\" and \"student\" to create the noun \"school student\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": " school student"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "ふゆ",
            "",
            "ほし"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to connect the nouns \"winter\" and \"star\" to create the noun \"winter star\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "winter star"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "くるま",
            "",
            "かいしゃ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to connect the nouns \"car\" and \"company\" to create the noun \"car company\"\n                ",
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": " car company"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "とけい",
            "",
            "かいしゃ"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to connect the nouns \"clock\" and \"company\" to create the noun \"clock company\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": " clock company"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "だいがく",
            "",
            "えいご",
            "",
            "せんせい"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "の",
            "の"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The の particle is needed to connect the nouns \"English\" and \"teacher\"\n                to create the noun \"English teacher\" and then you connect\n                this noun to \"University\" with the の particle to make the noun\n                \"university English teacher\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": " university English teacher"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "か Question Particle-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "か Question Particle",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Add it to the end of the sentence to make it a question",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "しゅくだいはなんですか？ (What is the homework?)"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 2",
            "explanation": "へやはさむいですか？ (Is the room cold?)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "そうです",
            "",
            "？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "か"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The か particle is needed after the です to turn the statement, \"That is so\"\n                into the question \"Is that so?\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " that so"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "こうこうせいです",
            "",
            "？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "か"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The か particle is needed after the です to turn the statement, \"You are a highschool student\"\n                into the question \"Are you a highschool student?\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Are"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " you a high school student"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "くるまはふつうです",
            "",
            "？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "か"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The か particle is needed after the です to turn the statement, \"The car is normal.\"\n                into the question \"Is the car normal?\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " the car normal"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "りゆうはなんです",
            "",
            "？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "か"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                As なん means \"what\", this generally implies\n                that the sentence is a question and such,\n                the か particle should be added after the です\n                to properly end a formal question in Japanese.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "What"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is the reason"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "にほんはおおきいです",
            "",
            "？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "か"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                The か particle is needed after the です to turn the statement, \"Japan is big.\"\n                into the question \"Is Japan big?\"\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " Japan big"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "?"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "〜時-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "〜じ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "(blank) o'clock",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "one o'clock, 1:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いちじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いちじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "one o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "1:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ichiji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "two o'clock, 2:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "にじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "にじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "two o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "2:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "three o'clock, 3:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さんじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さんじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "three o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "3:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "five o'clock, 5:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "five o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "5:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "six o'clock, 6:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ろくじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ろくじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "six o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "6:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "eight o'clock, 8:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はちじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はちじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eight o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "8:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "ten o'clock, 10:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ten o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "10:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "eleven o'clock, 11:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅういちじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅういちじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eleven o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "11:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "twelve o'clock, 12:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうにじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうにじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "twelve o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "12:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "四時-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よじ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "four o'clock, 4:00",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "four o'clock, 4:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "four o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "4:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yoji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "七時-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しちじ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "seven o'clock, 7:00",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "seven o'clock, 7:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しちじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しちじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "seven o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "7:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shichiji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "九時-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くじ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "nine o'clock, 9:00",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "nine o'clock, 9:00",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nine o'clock",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "9:00",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "何時-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なんじ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "what time, which hour",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "what time, which hour",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なんじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "なんじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "what time",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "which hour",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nanji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "〜分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "〜ふん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Counter for minutes",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example",
            "explanation": "にふん -> 2 minutes"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "two minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "にふん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "にふん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "two minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "2 minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nifun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "four minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よんふん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よんふん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "four minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "4 minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "five minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごふん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごふん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "five minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "5 minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "seven minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ななふん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ななふん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "seven minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "7 minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "nine minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きゅうふん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きゅうふん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nine minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "9 minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "一分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いっぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "one minute",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "one minute",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いっぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いっぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "one minute",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ippun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "三分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さんぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "three minutes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "three minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さんぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さんぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "three minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sanpun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "六分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ろっぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "six minutes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "six minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ろっぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ろっぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "six minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "roppun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "八分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "はっぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "eight minutes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "eight minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "はっぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "はっぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "eight minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "happun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "十分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゅっぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "ten minutes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "ten minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅっぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅっぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ten minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juppun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "何分-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "なんぷん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "How Many Minutes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "How Many Minutes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "なんぷん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "なんぷん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "how many minutes",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nanpun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "喫茶店-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きっさてん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Coffee Shop",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Coffee Shop",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きっさてん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きっさてん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "coffee shop",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kissaten",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "銀行-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぎんこう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bank",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bank",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぎんこう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ぎんこう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bank",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ginkou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "郵便局-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゆうびんきょく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Post Office",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Post Office",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ゆうびんきょく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ゆうびんきょく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "post office",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yuubinkyoku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "僕-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぼく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I, Me (Used more often by men)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I, Me (Used more often by men)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぼく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ぼく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "I",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "Me",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "I (Used more often by men)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "Me (Used more often by men)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "I, Me (Used more often by men)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "boku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "おれ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おれ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "I, Me (Used more often by men, esp. younger ones)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "I, Me (Used more often by men, esp. younger ones)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おれ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おれ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "I",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "Me",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "I (Used more often by men. younger ones)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "Me (Used more often by men. younger ones)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "I, Me (Used more often by men. younger ones)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ore",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "熊-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くま",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bear",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bear",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くま",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bear",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuma",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "綺麗-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きれい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Pretty",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Pretty",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きれい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きれい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pretty",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kirei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "明るい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あかるい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bright",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bright",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あかるい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あかるい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bright",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "akarui",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "子供-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こども",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Child, Kid",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Child, Kid",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こども",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "こども",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "child",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "kid",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kodomo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "うるさい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "うるさい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Annoying, Noisy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Annoying, Noisy",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "うるさい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "うるさい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "annoying",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "noisy",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "urusai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "こわい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "こわい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Scary",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Scary",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こわい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "こわい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "scary",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kowai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "よわい-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よわい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Weak",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Weak",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よわい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よわい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "weak",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yowai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "誰-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だれ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Who",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example",
            "explanation": "あなたはだれですか？ -> Who are you"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Who",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "だれ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "だれ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "who",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "dare",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "これ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "これ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "This (When referring to something close to you)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "これはおおきいですか？(Is this big?) -> You are asking if an object (close to you) is big"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はせいかくですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "これ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                This question refers to a guess \n                to an answer that you wrote so これ\n                is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Is "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "this"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " the correct answer?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はくまです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "これ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Using \"this\" in the sentence implies \n                that you are talking about a subject \n                that is near you so これ is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "This "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a bear."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "それ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "それ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That (When referring to something close to the person you are talking to)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "それはあなたのなまえですか(Is that your name?) -> In a way, their name is in their direction so you use それ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はへんですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "それ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Since \"that\" is used, you are referring to something that is closer to the \n                person you are talking to so それ is used in this case.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Is "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "that"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " weird?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はねこです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "それ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                \"That\" refers to a subject that is closer to the \n                person you are talking to so それ is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a cat."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "あれ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あれ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That lit. that over there (Used when talking about something far from you and the person you are talking to)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "あれはとしょかんです(That (over there) is a library) -> Using あれ implies that the library is far from you and the listener"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "は私の大学です。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あれ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                This version of \"that\" implies that you are talking \n                about the college which is far away from both you and the \n                speaker so あれ is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That (over there) "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " my university."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はやまですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あれ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                This version of \"that\" implies that you are talking \n                about a mountain which is far away from both you and the \n                speaker so あれ is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Is "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "that (over there)"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a mountain？"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "どれ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "どれ(が)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Which, Which one",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " どれがすきですか(Which do you like?) -> Question words such as which cannot be followed by a は particle so you must use が"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "",
            "あなたのくるまですか。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どれ",
            "が"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Which/Which one corresponds to どれ and question words such as どれ are  \n                followed by the particle が and not は\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Which one "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " your car."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "",
            "やすいですか"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どれ",
            "が"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Which/Which one corresponds to どれ and question words such as どれ are  \n                followed by the particle が and not は\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Which one "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " cheap"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "この-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "この",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "This (similar to これ but used when said right before a noun)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " このみせはたかいです。(This shop is expensive) -> Because \"this\" comes right before a noun, この is used and not これ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "がっこうはあたらしいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "この"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                これ and この mean \"this\" but since the noun \"school\" comes right after,\n                この is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "This"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " school is new."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はなはきれいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "この"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                これ and この mean \"this\" but since the noun \"flower\" comes right after,\n                この is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "This"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " flower is pretty."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "その-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "その",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That (Similar to それ but used when said right before a noun)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " そのさけはあたらしいです(That sake is new) -> Because \"that\" comes right before a noun, その is used and not それ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "みちはひろいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "その"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                それ and その mean \"that\" but since the noun \"street/road\" comes right after,\n                その is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " street/road is wide."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "りゆうはへんです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "その"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                それ and その mean \"that\" but since the noun \"reason\" comes right after,\n                その is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " reason is weird."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "あの-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あの",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That over there (Similar to あれ but used when said right before a noun)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " あのほしはおおきいです(That star (over there) is big) -> Because \"that (over there)\" comes right before a noun, あの is used and not あれ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "ひとはちいさいです"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                あれ and あの mean \"that\" but since the noun \"street/road\" comes right after,\n                あの is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " person (over there) is small."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "ほしはまぶしいです"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                あれ and あの mean \"that\" but since the noun \"star\" comes right after,\n                あの is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " star (over there) is bright."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "どの-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "どの",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "That over there (Similar to どれ but used when said right before a noun)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " どのいぬがつよいですか？(Which dog is strong?) -> Because \"which\" comes right before a noun, どの is used and not どれ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "さかな",
            "",
            "おいしいですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どの",
            "が"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                どれ and どの mean \"which\" but since the noun \"fish\" comes right after,\n                どの is used. Also, が must be used for question words like どの.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Which"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " fish "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " delicious?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "かいしゃ",
            "",
            "いいですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どの",
            "が"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                どれ and どの mean \"which\" but since the noun \"company\" comes right after,\n                どの is used. Also, が must be used for question words like どの.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Which"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " company "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " good?"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "も Also Particle-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "も Also/Too/As Well Particle",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "A particle similar to は except it adds the meaning \"also,\" \"too,\" or \"as well.\" Can be used to connect multiple verbs",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": " あなたもかわいいです。(You are also cute)"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 2",
            "explanation": "ふくもとけいもたかいです。(Clothes and watches are expensive too)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あなたのいけん",
            "",
            "ふつうです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "も"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Since this sentence is talking about your opinion \n                being normal too, も is used. \n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "Your opinion is normal "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "too."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "わたしのいぬ",
            "",
            "つよいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "も"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Since this sentence is talking about your dog also being strong,\n                も is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "My dog is "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "also"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " strong."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "えいごのしゅくだい",
            "",
            "むずかしいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "も"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                Since this sentence is talking about English homework\n                also being hard, も is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "English homework is "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "also"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " hard."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "も Both Particle-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ＡもＢも",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Both A and B",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "ふくもとけいもたかいです。(Both clothes and watches are expensive)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あお",
            "",
            "あか",
            "",
            "いいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "も",
            "も"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since we are talking about both blue and \n                    red being good, the も particle is used \n                    after both nouns.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Both"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " blue and red are good."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あなた",
            "",
            "わたしのともだち",
            "",
            "いしゃです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "も",
            "も"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since we are talking about both you and my\n                    friend being doctors, the も particle is \n                    used after both nouns.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Both"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " you and my friend are doctors."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "食べる-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "たべる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To eat",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To eat",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "たべる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "たべる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to eat",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "taberu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "わかる-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "わかる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To understand",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To understand",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "わかる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "わかる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to understand",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "wakaru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "見る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "みる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To see",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To see",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "みる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "みる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to see",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "miru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "寝る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ねる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To sleep",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To sleep",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ねる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ねる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to sleep",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "neru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "起きる-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おきる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To wake up, To occur, To happen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To wake up, To occur, To happen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おきる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おきる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to wake up",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to occur",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to happen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "okiru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "考える-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かんがえる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To consider",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To consider",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かんがえる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かんがえる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to consider",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kangaeru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "出る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "でる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To leave, To come out",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To leave, To come out",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "でる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "でる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to leave",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "to come out",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "deru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "借りる-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かりる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To borrow, To rent",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To borrow, To rent",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かりる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かりる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to borrow",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to rent",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kariru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "着る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To wear (for upper body clothing)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples",
            "explanation": "This word is used for clothes such as shirts, jackets, tank tops etc."
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To wear (for upper body clothing)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to wear",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "to wear (for upper body clothing)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kiru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "聞く-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "きく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To hear, To listen",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To hear, To listen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "きく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "きく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to hear",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "to listen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kiku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "泳ぐ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "およぐ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To swim",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To swim",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "およぐ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "およぐ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to swim",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oyogu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "遊ぶ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あそぶ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To play",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To play",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あそぶ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あそぶ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to play",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "asobu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "買う-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To buy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To buy",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to buy",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kau",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "する-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "する",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To do",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To do",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "する",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "する",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to do",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "suru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "死ぬ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しぬ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To die, To pass away",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To die, To pass away",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しぬ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しぬ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to die",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "to pass away",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shinu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "来る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To come",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To come",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to come",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kuru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "読む-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "よむ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To read",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To read",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よむ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "よむ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to read",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yomu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "帰る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かえる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To return, To come home, To go home",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To return, To come home, To go home",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かえる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かえる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to return",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to come home",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "to go home",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "to change",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Although かえる in Hiragana can have this meaning as well, we are looking for a different meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaeru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "行く-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To go",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To go",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to go",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "iku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "使う-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "つかう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To use",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To use",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "つかう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "つかう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to use",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tsukau",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "作る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "つくる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To make",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To make",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "つくる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "つくる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to make",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tsukuru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "思う-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おもう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To think",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To think",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おもう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おもう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to think",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "omou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "知る-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しる",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "To know",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "To know",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しる",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しる",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to know",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shiru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ここ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ここ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Here, This place",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "ここはわたしのこうこうです (This place is my highschool)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はわたしのいえです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ここ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    We are talking about a place that is close to you (here) so \n                    ここ is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "This place"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is my house."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "ひとはたのしいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ここの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    More specifically than here, we are talking about \n                    the people here so you use ここ and add a の\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The people "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "here"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " are fun."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "そこ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "そこ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "There, That Place",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "そこのひとはやさしいです。(The people there are nice)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "ゆうびんきょくはふるいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "そこの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    More specifically than there, we are talking about \n                    the post office there so you use そこ and add a の\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The post office "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "there"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is old."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "としょかんのひとはこわいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "そこの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    More specifically than there, we are talking about \n                    the library there so you use そこ and add a の\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The people in that library "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "there"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " are scary."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "あそこ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あそこ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "(over) there, That place (over there)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "あそこはあぶないです。 (It is dangerous over there)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "だいがくはきれいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あそこの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    More specifically than over there, we are talking about\n                    the library over there so we use あそこ and add a の\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The university "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "over there"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is pretty."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "のきっさてんはたかいです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あそこ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    More specifically than over there, we are talking about\n                    the coffee shop over there so we use あそこ and add a の\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "The coffee shop "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "over there"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is expensive."
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "はあついです。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "あそこ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    We are talking about a place over there so あそこ is used\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "That place (over there)"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is hot."
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "どこ-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "どこ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Where",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "うみはどこですか？ (Where is the ocean?)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "ねこは",
            "",
            "ですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どこ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since we are asking \"where\", どこ is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Where"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is the cat?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "つくえは",
            "",
            "ですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どこ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since we are asking \"where\", どこ is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Where"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is the desk?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あなたのいえは",
            "",
            "ですか？"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "どこ"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since we are asking \"where\", どこ is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Where"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " is your house?"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "だれの-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だれの + noun",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Whose X",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Breakdown",
            "explanation": "This is a combination of the word for who (だれ) and the の particle indicating possession"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "それはだれのほんですか (Whose book is that)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あれは",
            "",
            "くるまですか"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "だれの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                We are asking about whose car it is, so we use だれの。\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Whose"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " car is that?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "これは",
            "",
            "へやですか"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "だれの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                We are asking about whose room it is, so we use だれの。\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Whose"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " room is this?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "それは",
            "",
            "とけいですか"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "だれの"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                We are asking about whose watch it is, so we use だれの\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "Whose"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " watch is that?"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "じゃないです-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゃないです",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (formal for nouns and な adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "わたしはがくせいじゃないです。(I am not a student)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "これはわたしのしゅくだい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "じゃないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal but not very formal\n                    and we are talking about homework, which is a noun, \n                    じゃないです is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "This "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " my homework. (formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、ここはきっさてん",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "じゃないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal but not very formal\n                    and we are talking about a coffee shop, which is a noun, じゃないです is used. \n                    Also, for non-casual sentences, いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", this place "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a coffee shop. (formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、ぼくはえいごのせんせい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "じゃないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal but not very formal \n                    and we are talking about being an English teacher, which is a noun, \n                    じゃないです is used. Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", I "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "am not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " an English teacher. (formal)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ではありません-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ではありません",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (very formal for nouns and な adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "わたしはがくせいではありません。 (I am not a student)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、これはわたしのしゅくだい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "ではありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is very formal and we are \n                    talking about homework, which is a noun,\n                    ではありません is used. Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", this "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " my homework. (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "ここはきっさてん",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ではありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is very formal and we are talking \n                    about a coffee shop, which is a noun, \n                    ではありません is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "This place "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a coffee shop. (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、わたしのりょうしんはえいごのせんせい",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "ではありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is very formal and we are \n                    talking about parents being an English teacher, which is a noun,\n                    ではありません is used. Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", my parents "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "are not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " English teachers. (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "じゃない-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゃない",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (casual  for nouns and な adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "あれはくまじゃない。 (That over there is not a bear)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "おれはいしゃ",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "じゃない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual\n                    and we are talking about being a doctor, \n                    which is a noun, じゃない is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "I "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "am not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a doctor. (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、そこのひとはこども",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ううん",
            "じゃない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual and we are talking \n                    about kids, which is a noun, \n                    じゃない is used. Also, for casual sentences,\n                    ううん is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", the people there "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "are not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " kids. (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、それはおれのなまえ",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ううん",
            "じゃない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual and we are talking \n                    about someone's name which is a noun, \n                    じゃない is used. Also, for casual sentences,\n                    ううん is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", that "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " my name. (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "それはすこし",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "じゃない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual\n                    and we are talking about something being a small amount, \n                    which is a な-adjective, \n                    じゃない is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "That "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a little. (casual)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "くない-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くない",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (casual for い-adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Rule",
            "explanation": "Remove the い and replace it with くない, e.g. よわい -> よわくない"
          },
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "ううん、えいごはたのしくない (No, English is not fun)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "ぼくは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ちいさくない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual and ちいさい \n                    is a い-adjective, くない is used. To make ちいさい\n                    negative: ちいさい -> ちいさくない\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "I "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "am not small"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " . (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、いまは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ううん",
            "わるくない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual and わるい is \n                    an い-adjective, くない is used. To make \n                    わるい negative: わるい -> わるくない\n                    Also, for casual sentences,\n                    ううん is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", right now "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not bad"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、いまのわたしのくるまは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ううん",
            "ふるくない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual and ふるい is \n                    an い-adjective, くない is used. To make \n                    ふるい negative: ふるい -> ふるくない\n                    Also, for casual sentences,\n                    ううん is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", my current car "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not old"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (casual)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "それはすこし",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "じゃない"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is casual\n                    and we are talking about something being a small amount, \n                    which is a な-adjective, \n                    じゃない is used.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "That "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": " a little. (casual)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "くないです-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くないです",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (formal for い-adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "くまはこわくないです (Bears are not scary)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あのぎんこうは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "ちいさくないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal but not very formal and ちいさい \n                    is a い-adjective, くないです is used. To make ちいさい\n                    negative: ちいさい -> ちいさくない\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "That bank "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not small"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、あのゆうびんきょくは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "ちかくないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal and ちかい is \n                    an い-adjective, くないです is used. To make \n                    ちかい negative: ちかい -> ちかくないです\n                    Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", that post office "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not close"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、わたしのともだちは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "よわくないです"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal and よわい is \n                    an い-adjective, くないです is used. To make \n                    よわい negative: よわい -> よわくない\n                    Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", my friend "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not weak"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (formal)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "くありません-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Grammar",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くありません",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Not (very formal for い-adjectives)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": "あしたはさむくありません。(Tomorrow is not cold)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "あのくには",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "とおくありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is very formal and and とおい \n                    is a い-adjective, くありません is used. To make とおい\n                    negative: とおい -> とおくありません\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": "That country "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not far"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、そのりゆうは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "わるくありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal and わるい is \n                    an い-adjective, くありません is used. To make \n                    わるい negative: わるい -> わるくありません\n                    Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", that reason"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": " is not bad"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Properly fill in the blanks to connect the sentence",
          "question": [
            "",
            "、このみせは",
            "",
            "。"
          ],
          "answer": [
            "いいえ",
            "たかくありません"
          ],
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "\n                    Since this sentence is formal and たかい is \n                    an い-adjective, くありません is used. To make \n                    たかい negative: たかい -> たかくありません\n                    Also, for non-casual sentences,\n                    いいえ is used for no.\n                ",
          "englishTranslation": [
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "No"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ", this shop "
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": true,
              "text": "is not expensive"
            },
            {
              "partToTranslate": false,
              "text": ". (very formal)"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ア-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ア",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "あ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "イ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "イ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "い",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "イ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "い",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ウ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ウ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "う",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ウ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "う",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "エ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "エ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "え",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "エ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "え",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "オ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "オ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "お",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "オ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "お",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "カ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "カ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "か",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "カ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "か",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "キ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "キ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "き",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "キ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "き",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ク-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ク",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "く",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ク",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "く",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ケ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ケ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "け",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ケ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "け",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "コ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "コ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "こ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "コ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "こ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "サ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "サ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "さ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "サ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "シ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "シ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "し",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "シ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "し",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ス-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ス",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "す",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "す",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "セ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "セ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "せ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "セ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "せ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ソ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ソ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "そ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ソ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "そ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "タ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "タ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "た",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "タ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "た",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "チ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "チ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ち",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "チ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ち",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ツ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ツ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "つ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ツ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "つ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "テ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "テ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "て",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "テ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "て",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ト-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ト",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "と",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ト",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "と",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ナ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ナ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "な",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ナ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "な",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ニ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ニ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "に",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ニ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "に",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヌ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヌ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぬ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヌ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぬ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ネ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ネ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ね",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ネ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ね",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ノ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ノ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "の",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ノ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "の",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ハ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ハ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "は",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ハ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "は",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヒ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヒ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ひ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヒ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "フ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "フ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ふ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "フ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ふ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "へ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "へ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "へ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "hint",
            "explanation": "They are the exact same"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "へ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "へ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ホ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ホ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ほ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ホ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ほ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "マ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "マ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ま",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "マ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ま",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ミ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ミ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "み",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ミ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "み",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ム-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ム",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "む",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ム",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "む",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "メ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "メ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "め",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "メ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "め",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "モ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "モ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "も",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "hint",
            "explanation": "They are very similar except モ has much more sharper edges (as is normal with katakana)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "モ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "も",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ネクタイ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ネクタイ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tie, Necktie",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tie, Necktie",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ネクタイ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ネクタイ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tie",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "necktie",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nekutai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "マイク-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "マイク",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mic, Microphone",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mic, Microphone",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "マイク",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "マイク",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mic",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "microphone",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "maiku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "マイナス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "マイナス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Minus, Negative (number)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Minus, Negative (number)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "マイナス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "マイナス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "minus",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "negative",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "negative (number)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mainasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "メモ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "メモ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Note, Memo",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Note, Memo",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "メモ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "メモ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "note",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "memo",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "memo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "マスク-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "マスク",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Face Mask 😷, Mask",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Face Mask 😷, Mask",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "マスク",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "マスク",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "face mask",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "mask",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "masuku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヤ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヤ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "や",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヤ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "や",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ユ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ユ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ゆ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ユ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ゆ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヨ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヨ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "よ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヨ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "よ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ラ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ラ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ら",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ラ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ら",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "リ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "リ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "り",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "リ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "り",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ル-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ル",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "る",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ル",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "る",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "レ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "レ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "れ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "レ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "れ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ロ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ロ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ろ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ロ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ろ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ワ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ワ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "わ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ワ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "わ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ン-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ン",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ん",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "アイロン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "アイロン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Iron (for pressing clothes)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Iron (for pressing clothes)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "アイロン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "アイロン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "iron",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "iron (for pressing clothes)",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "airon",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "レストラン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "レストラン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Restaurant",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Restaurant",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "レストラン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "レストラン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "restaurant",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "resutoran",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "カラオケ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "カラオケ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Karaoke",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Karaoke",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "カラオケ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "カラオケ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "karaoke",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "karaoke",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "アニメ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "アニメ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Cartoon, Anime",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Cartoon, Anime",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "アニメ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "アニメ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "cartoon",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "anime",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "anime",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ウイルス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ウイルス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Virus",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Virus",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ウイルス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ウイルス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "virus",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "uirusu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ストレス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ストレス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Stress",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Stress",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ストレス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ストレス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "stress",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sutoresu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "カメラ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "カメラ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Camera",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Camera",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "カメラ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "カメラ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "camera",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kamera",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "トイレ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "トイレ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Restroom (Casual)",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Restroom",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "トイレ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "トイレ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "restroom",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "restroom (casual)",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "toire",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ホテル-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ホテル",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hotel",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hotel",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ホテル",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ホテル",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hotel",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hoteru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ハンカチ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ハンカチ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Handkerchief",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Handkerchief",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ハンカチ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ハンカチ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "handkerchief",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hankachi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ァ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ァ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small ア",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "ファ -> fa, ツァ -> tsa"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ファ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fa",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ツァ",
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false,
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tsa",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "ィ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ィ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Small イ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "ウィ -> wi, フィ -> fi, ディ -> di"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ウィ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "フィ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fi",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ディ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "di",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ティ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ti",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゥ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゥ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "ウ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "トゥ -> to (pronounced like two), ドゥ -> do (pronounced like dew)"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "トゥ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "to",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ドゥ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "do",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ェ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ェ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "エ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "ウェ -> we, シェ -> she,  ジェ -> je"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ウェ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "we",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "シェ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "she",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ジェ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "je",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "フェ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fe",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "チェ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "che",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ォ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ォ",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "オ",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples:",
            "explanation": "フォ -> fo, ウォ -> wo"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "フォ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Romaji",
          "question": "ウォ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wo",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ー-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ー (long vowel mark)",
        "explanationHeader": "Explanation",
        "explanation": "Extends the consonant(あいうえお sound) right before it",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Pronunciation Examples:",
            "explanation": "イー -> いい, フー -> ふう, ター -> たあ"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ユー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ゆう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ネー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ねえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "マー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "まあ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "シー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "エー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ええ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ファイル-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ファイル",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "File",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "File",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ファイル",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ファイル",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "file",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fuairu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ファン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ファン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fan",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fan",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ファン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ファン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fan",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fuan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "アイスクリーム-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "アイスクリーム",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ice Cream",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Ice Cream",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "アイスクリーム",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "アイスクリーム",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ice cream",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "aisukuriimu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "オーケー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "オーケー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Ok, Okay",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Ok, Okay",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "オーケー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "オーケー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ok",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "okay",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ookee",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "スカート-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "スカート",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Skirt",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Skirt",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "スカート",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "スカート",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "skirt",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sukaato",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "タクシー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "タクシー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Taxi",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Taxi",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "タクシー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "タクシー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "taxi",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "takushii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ソファー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ソファー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sofa",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sofa",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ソファー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ソファー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sofa",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sofuaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "フォーク-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "フォーク",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Fork",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Fork",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "フォーク",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "フォーク",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "fork",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "fuooku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "モーテル-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "モーテル",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Motel",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Motel",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "モーテル",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "モーテル",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "motel",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mooteru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ガ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ガ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "が",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ガ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "が",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ギ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ギ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぎ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ギ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぎ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "グ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "グ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぐ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "グ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぐ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゲ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゲ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "げ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ゲ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "げ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゴ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゴ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ご",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ゴ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ご",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ザ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ザ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ざ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ザ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ざ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ジ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ジ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "じ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ジ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ズ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ズ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ず",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ズ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ず",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゼ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゼ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぜ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ゼ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぜ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゾ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゾ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぞ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ゾ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぞ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ダ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ダ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "だ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ダ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "だ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヂ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヂ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぢ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヂ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぢ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ヅ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ヅ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "づ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ヅ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "づ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "デ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "デ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "で",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "デ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "で",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ド-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ド",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ど",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ド",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ど",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "バ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "バ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ば",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "バ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ば",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ビ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ビ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "び",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ビ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "び",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ブ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ブ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぶ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ブ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぶ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ベ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ベ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ベ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "べ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "べ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ボ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ボ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぼ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ボ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぼ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "パ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "パ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぱ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "パ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぱ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ピ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ピ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぴ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ピ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぴ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "プ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "プ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぷ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "プ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぷ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ぺ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぺ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぺ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ぺ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぺ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "ポ-カタカナ": {
      "conceptType": "Katakana",
      "isFastReviewCard": true,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ポ",
        "explanationHeader": "Corresponding Hiragana",
        "explanation": "ぽ",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Hiragana",
          "question": "ポ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぽ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        }
      ]
    },
    "アルバイト-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "アルバイト",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Part Time Job, Part-Time Job",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Part Time Job, Part-Time Job",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "アルバイト",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "アルバイト",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "part time job",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "part-time Job",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "arubaito",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "テレビ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "テレビ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Television, TV",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Television, TV",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "テレビ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "テレビ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "television",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "tv",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "terebi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ドラマ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ドラマ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Drama",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Drama",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ドラマ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ドラマ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "drama",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "dorama",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ジュース-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ジュース",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Juice",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Juice",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ジュース",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ジュース",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "juice",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "juusu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "スーパー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "スーパー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Supermarket",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Supermarket",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "スーパー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "スーパー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "supermarket",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "suupaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "メーク-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "メーク",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Makeup, Make-up",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Makeup, Make-up",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "メーク",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "メーク",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "makeup",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "make-up",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "meeku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "パソコン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "パソコン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Personal Computer, PC",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Personal Computer, PC",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "パソコン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "パサコン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Personal Computer",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            },
            {
              "answer": "pc",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "pasakon",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "フランス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "フランス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "France",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "France",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "フランス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "フランス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "France",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "furansu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "カナダ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "カナダ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Canada",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Canada",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "カナダ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "カナダ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Canada",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kanada",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "メキシコ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "メキシコ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mexico",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mexico",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "メキシコ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "メキシコ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Mexico",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mekishiko",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ちゅうごく-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ちゅうごく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "China",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "China",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ちゅうごく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ちゅうごく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "China",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "chuugoku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "かんこく-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かんこく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Korea",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Korea",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かんこく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かんこく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Korea",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kankoku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "スペイン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "スペイン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Spain",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Spain",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "スペイン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "スペイン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Spain",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "supein",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "イタリア-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "イタリア",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Italy",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Italy",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "イタリア",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "イタリア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Italy",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "itaria",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ロシア-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ロシア",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Russia",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Russia",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ロシア",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ロシア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Russia",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "roshia",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "オーストラリア-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "オーストラリア",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Australia",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Australia",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "オーストラリア",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "オーストラリア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Australia",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oosutoraria",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ドイツ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ドイツ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Germany",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Germany",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ドイツ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ドイツ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Germany",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "doitsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "イギリス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "イギリス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "United Kingdom",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "United Kingdom",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "イギリス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "イギリス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "United Kingdom",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "igirisu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "オーストリア-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "オーストリア",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Austria",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Austria",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "オーストリア",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "オーストリア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Austria",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oosutoria",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "タイ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "タイ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thailand",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thailand",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "タイ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "タイ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Thailand",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "サウジアラビア-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "サウジアラビア",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Saudi Arabia",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Saudi Arabia",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "サウジアラビア",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "サウジアラビア",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Saudi Arabia",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "saujiarabia",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ギリシャ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ギリシャ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Greece",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Greece",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ギリシャ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ギリシャ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Greece",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "girisha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "インド-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "インド",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "India",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "India",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "インド",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "インド",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "India",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "indo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ブラジル-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ブラジル",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Brazil",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Brazil",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ブラジル",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ブラジル",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Brazil",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "burajiru",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ベトナム-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ベトナム",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Vietnam",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Vietnam",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ベトナム",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ベトナム",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Vietnam",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "betonamu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "アメリカ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "アメリカ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "America",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "America",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "アメリカ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "アメリカ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "America",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "amerika",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "スウェーデン-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "スウェーデン",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sweden",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sweden",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "スウェーデン",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "スウェーデン",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Sweden",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "suueeden",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an う Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ます",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an う Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Change the last character of the verb to its い sound and add ます",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "Example 1",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "読",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "よ"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "む"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "読",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "よ"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "みます"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  " The み is turned into a む."
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "Don't know verb groups?",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "For More Details",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  "Read this article on ",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "a",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "href": "/articles/verbs/verbs-dictionary-form-and-verb-groups",
                      "children": "ます form"
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "More info on ます form",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "For More Info",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  "Read this article on ",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "a",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "href": "/articles/verbs/verbs-masu-form",
                      "children": "ます form"
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To hear, To listen (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "聞きます",
            "kana": "ききます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "きく",
                " -> ",
                "き",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "く"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "き",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To swim (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "泳ぐぎます",
            "kana": "およぎます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "およぐ",
                " -> ",
                "およ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "ぐ"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "ぎ",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To play (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "遊ぶびます",
            "kana": "あそびます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "あそぶ",
                " -> ",
                "あそ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "ぶ"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "び",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To drink (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "飲みます",
            "kana": "のみます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "のむ",
                " -> ",
                "の",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "む"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "み",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To buy (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "買います",
            "kana": "かいます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "かう",
                " -> ",
                "か",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "う"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "い",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To read (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "読みます",
            "kana": "よみます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an い sound and add a ます. ",
                "よむ",
                " -> ",
                "よ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "む"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "み",
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an る Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ます",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an る Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Remove the last character of the verb and add ます",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "Example 1",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "見",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "み"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "る"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "見",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "み"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "ます"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  " The る is removed and a ます is added."
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "Don't know verb groups?",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "For More Details",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  "Read this article on ",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "a",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "href": "/articles/verbs/verbs-dictionary-form-and-verb-groups",
                      "children": "ます form"
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "More info on ます form",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "For More Info",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  "Read this article on ",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "a",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "href": "/articles/verbs/verbs-masu-form",
                      "children": "ます form"
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To eat (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "食べます",
            "kana": "たべます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "たべる",
                " -> ",
                "たべ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To sleep (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "寝ます",
            "kana": "ねます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "ねる",
                " -> ",
                "ね",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To see (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "見ます",
            "kana": "みます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "みる",
                " -> ",
                "み",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To consider (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "考えます",
            "kana": "かんがえます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "かんがえる",
                " -> ",
                "かんがえ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To wake up (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "起きます",
            "kana": "おきます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "おきる",
                " -> ",
                "おき",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To leave, To come out (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "出ます",
            "kana": "でます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "でる",
                " -> ",
                "で",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To borrow, To rent (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "借ります",
            "kana": "かります"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ます. ",
                "かりる",
                " -> ",
                "かり",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ます"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an Irregular Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ます",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an Irregular Verb to Formal Present Tense (ます Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "There is no pattern, you just memorize the 2 rules in the below examples.",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "First Verb",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": null,
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": "する -> します"
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "Second Verb",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": null,
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "来",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "く"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "る"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "来",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "き"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "ます"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "For More Details",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": null,
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  "Read this article on ",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "a",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "href": "/articles/verbs/verbs-masu-form",
                      "children": "ます form"
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To do (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "します",
            "kana": "します"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "Since this is a irregular verb, we can just memorize \n    the fact that the ます form of する is します"
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "To come (formal)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "来ます",
            "kana": "きます"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "Since this is a irregular verb, we can just memorize \n    the fact that the ます form of くる is きます"
        }
      ]
    },
    "前-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "まえ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Before, In front of",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Before, In front of",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "まえ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "まえ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "before",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "in front of",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mae",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "とんかつ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "とんかつ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tonkatsu, Pork Cutlet",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tonkatsu, Pork Cutlet",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "とんかつ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "とんかつ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tonkatsu",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "pork cutlet",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tonkatsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "メニュー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "メニュー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Menu",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Menu",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "メニュー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "メニュー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "menu",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "menyuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "鉛筆-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "えんぴつ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Pencil",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Pencil",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "えんぴつ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "えんぴつ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "pencil",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "enpitsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "傘-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かさ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Umbrella",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Umbrella",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かさ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かさ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "umbrella",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kasa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "かばん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かばん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bag, Satchel, Briefcase",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bag, Satchel, Briefcase",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かばん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かばん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bag",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "satchel",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "briefcase",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaban",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "靴-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "くつ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Shoe, Shoes",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Shoe, Shoes",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "くつ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "くつ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "shoe",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "shoes",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kutsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "財布-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "さいふ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Wallet",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Wallet",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "さいふ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "さいふ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "wallet",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "saifu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ジーンズ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ジーンズ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Jeans",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Jeans",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ジーンズ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ジーンズ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "jeans",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "jiinzu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "辞書-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じしょ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Dictionary",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Dictionary",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じしょ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じしょ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "dictionary",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "jisho",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "自転車-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じてんしゃ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Bicycle, Bike",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Bicycle, Bike",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じてんしゃ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じてんしゃ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "bicycle",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "bike",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "jitensha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "新聞-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "しんぶん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Newspaper",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Newspaper",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "しんぶん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "しんぶん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "newspaper",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "shinbun",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "テープ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "テープ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tape",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tape",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "テープ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "テープ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tape",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "teepu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "トレーナー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "トレーナー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Trainer",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Trainer",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "トレーナー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "トレーナー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "trainer",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "toreenaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ノート-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ノート",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Notebook",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Notebook",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ノート",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ノート",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "notebook",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "nooto",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "帽子-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぼうし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hat, Cap",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hat, Cap",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぼうし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ぼうし",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "hat",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "cap",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "boushi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お手洗い-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おてあらい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Restroom",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Restroom",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おてあらい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おてあらい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "restroom",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "otearai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "経済-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "けいざい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Economy, Economics",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Economy, Economics",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "けいざい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "けいざい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "economy",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "economics",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "keizai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "いくら-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いくら",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "How much",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "How much",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いくら",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いくら",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "how much",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ikura",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "〜円-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "〜えん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Counter for yen",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example",
            "explanation": "ひゃくえん -> 100 yen"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "1 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いちえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "5 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "10 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゅうえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "50 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごじゅうえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "100 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひゃくえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "500 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ごひゃくえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "1000 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "せんえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "10000 yen",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いちまんえん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いちえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "1 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "one yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ichien",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "5 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "five yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゅうえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "10 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "ten yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ひゃくえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "100 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "one hundred yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごひゃくえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "500 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "five hundred yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "せんえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "1000 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "one thousand yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ごじゅうえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "50 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "fifty yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いちまんえん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "10000 yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "ten thousand yen",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "いらっしゃいませ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いらっしゃいませ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Welcome",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Situations used in",
            "explanation": "This is used by shops, restaurants, etc when a customer enters"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Welcome",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いらっしゃいませ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いらっしゃいませ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "welcome",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "irasshaimase",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "おねがいします-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おねがいします",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Please, Please (very formall)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples where this is used",
            "explanation": "When you are at a restaurant asking the server for a check"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Please",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おねがいします",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おねがいします",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "please",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "onegaishimasu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ください-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ください",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Please, Please (formal)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Examples where this is used",
            "explanation": "When you are making a request to someone you don't know"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Please",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ください",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ください",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "please",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kudasai",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "じゃあ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "じゃあ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Then, Well, So, Well then",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Then, Well, So, Well then",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "じゃあ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "じゃあ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "then",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "well",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "so",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            },
            {
              "answer": "well then",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "jaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "どうぞ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "どうぞ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Here you go, Go ahead",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Here you go, Go ahead",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "どうぞ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "どうぞ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "here you go",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "go ahead",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "douzo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "どうも-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "どうも",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Thank you (more casual)",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "どうも vs ありがとう",
            "explanation": "どうも is more casual"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Thank you (more casual)",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "どうも",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ありがとう",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "We are looking for something even more casual",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "どうも",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "thank you",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            },
            {
              "answer": "thank you (more casual)",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "doumo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "番号-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ばんごう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Number",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Number",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ばんごう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ばんごう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "number",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bangou",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "留学-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "りゅうがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Study abroad, Studying abroad",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Study abroad, Studying abroad",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "りゅうがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "りゅうがく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "study abroad",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "studying abroad",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ryuugaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "留学生-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "りゅうがくせい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Study abroad student, Exchange student",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Study abroad student, Exchange student",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "りゅうがくせい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "りゅうがくせい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "study abroad student",
              "distanceToAllow": 8
            },
            {
              "answer": "exchange student",
              "distanceToAllow": 7
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ryuugakusei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "科学-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Science",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Important note",
            "explanation": "This word also means chemistry however their kanji is different and we are focused on the \"science\" meaning for this case"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Science",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かがく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "science",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "chemistry",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Although the hiragana for \"chemistry\" is かがく we are looking for a different, but related word",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kagaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "コンピューター-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "コンピューター",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Computer",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Computer",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "コンピューター",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "コンピューター",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "computer",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "konpyuutaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "政治-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "せいじ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Politics",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Politics",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "せいじ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "せいじ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "politics",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "seiji",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ビジネス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ビジネス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Business",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Business",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ビジネス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ビジネス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "business",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bijinesu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "文学-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ぶんがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Literature",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Literature",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ぶんがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ぶんがく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "literature",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bungaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "歴史-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "れきし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "History",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "History",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "れきし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "れきし",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "history",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "rekishi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "数学-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "すうがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mathematics",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mathematics",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "すうがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "すうがく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mathematics",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "suugaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "会社員-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "かいしゃいん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Company employee, Office worker",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Company employee, Office worker",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "かいしゃいん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "かいしゃいん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Company employee",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            },
            {
              "answer": "Office worker",
              "distanceToAllow": 5
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "kaishain",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "大学院-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だいがくいん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Graduate school",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Graduate school",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "だいがくいん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "だいがくいん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "graduate school",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "daigakuin",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "大学院生-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "だいがくいんせい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Graduate student",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Graduate student",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "だいがくいんせい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "だいがくいんせい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "graduate student",
              "distanceToAllow": 6
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "daigakuinsei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "弁護士-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "べんごし",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Lawyer, Attorney",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Lawyer, Attorney",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "べんごし",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "べんごし",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "lawyer",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "attorney",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bengoshi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お母さん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おかあさん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Mother, Mom",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "The お is added for politeness. かあさん has the same meaning as well but not with the same level of politeness"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Mother, Mom",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おかあさん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "かあさん",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is the more polite way to say mother?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おかあさん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "mother",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "mom",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "okaasan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お父さん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おとうさん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Father, Dad",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "The お is added for politeness. とうさん has the same meaning as well but not with the same level of politeness"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Father, Dad",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おとうさん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "とうさん",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is the more polite way to say father?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おとうさん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "father",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            },
            {
              "answer": "dad",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "otousan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お姉さん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おねえさん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Older sister",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "The お is added for politeness. ねえさん has the same meaning as well but not with the same level of politeness"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Older sister",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おねえさん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ねえさん",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is the more polite way to say older sister?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おねえさん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "older sister",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oneesan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お兄さん-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おにいさん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Older brother",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Note",
            "explanation": "The お is added for politeness. おにいさん has the same meaning as well but not with the same level of politeness"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Older brother",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おにいさん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "おにいさん",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is the more polite way to say older brother?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おにいさん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "older brother",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oniisan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "妹-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いもうと",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Younger sister, Little sister",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Younger sister, Little sister",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いもうと",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いもうと",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "younger sister",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "little sister",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "imouto",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "弟-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おとうと",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Younger brother, Little brother",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Younger brother, Little brother",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おとうと",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おとうと",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "younger brother",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            },
            {
              "answer": "little brother",
              "distanceToAllow": 4
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "otouto",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "姪-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "めい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Niece",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Niece",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "めい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "めい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "niece",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "mei",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "甥-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おい",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Nephew",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Same Hiragana",
            "explanation": "This word has the same hiragana as the word \"hey\" but the kanji are different"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Nephew",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おい",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おい",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "nephew",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hey",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Although they use the same hiragana, in this question we are looking for the word that is related to family",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "oi",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "いとこ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "いとこ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Cousin",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Cousin",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "いとこ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "いとこ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "cousin",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "itoko",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "映画-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "えいが",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Movie",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Movie",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "えいが",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "えいが",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "movie",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "eiga",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "音楽-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おんがく",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Music",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Music",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おんがく",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おんがく",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "music",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ongaku",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "スポーツ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "スポーツ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Sport, Sports",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Sport, Sports",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "スポーツ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "スポーツ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "sport",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "sports",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "supootsu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "テニス-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "テニス",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tennis",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tennis",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "テニス",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "テニス",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tennis",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "tenisu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "サッカー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "サッカー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Soccer, Football",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Soccer, Football",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "サッカー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "サッカー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "soccer",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            },
            {
              "answer": "football",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "sakkaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ゴルフ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ゴルフ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Golf",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Golf",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ゴルフ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ゴルフ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "golf",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "gorufu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "野球-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "やきゅう",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Baseball",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Baseball",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "やきゅう",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "やきゅう",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "baseball",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "yakyuu",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "デート-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "デート",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Date",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "context",
            "explanation": "This is used in the romantic sense. E.g \"Date with my partner\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Date",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "デート",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "デート",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "date",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "deeto",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ビデオ-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ビデオ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Video",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Video",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ビデオ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ビデオ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "video",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bideo",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "朝ご飯-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "あさごはん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Breakfast",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Formality",
            "explanation": "This is the casual way to say \"breakfast\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Breakfast",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "あさごはん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ちょうしょく",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is a more casual way to say breakfast?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "あさごはん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "breakfast",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "asagohan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "昼ご飯-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ひるごはん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Lunch",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Formality",
            "explanation": "This is the casual way to say \"lunch\""
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Lunch",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ひるごはん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ひるごはん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "lunch",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ちゅうしょく",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "What is a more casual way to say breakfast?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            },
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hirugohan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "晩御飯-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ばんごはん",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Dinner",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Dinner",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ばんごはん",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ばんごはん",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "dinner",
              "distanceToAllow": 1
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "bangohan",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "お茶-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "おちゃ",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Tea",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "formality",
            "explanation": "\n            Although the お is for formality and ちゃ is \n            also technically correct, practically speaking, \n            nobody says ちゃ so it would be best to always use おちゃ\n            "
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Tea",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "おちゃ",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ちゃ",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Although this doesn mean \"tea\", this way of saying it is very used. What is the more common way?",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": true
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "おちゃ",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "tea",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "ocha",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "コーヒー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "コーヒー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Coffee",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Coffee",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "コーヒー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "コーヒー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "coffee",
              "distanceToAllow": 2
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "koohii",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "ハンバーガー-単語": {
      "conceptType": "Vocabulary",
      "isFastReviewCard": false,
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "ハンバーガー",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Hamburger",
        "extraInfoList": []
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding Japanese word",
          "question": "Hamburger",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "ハンバーガー",
              "distanceToAllow": 0
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [],
          "answerIsInJapanese": true
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": " the corresponding English word",
          "question": "ハンバーガー",
          "answers": [
            {
              "answer": "Hamburger",
              "distanceToAllow": 3
            }
          ],
          "acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor": [
            {
              "acceptableResponse": "hanbaagaa",
              "whyNotLookingFor": "Please enter the vocabulary's meaning",
              "acceptableResponseIsJapanese": false
            }
          ],
          "answerIsInJapanese": false
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an う Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ない",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an う Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Change the last character of the verb to its あ sound and add ない. This changes the verb to mean to \"not\" do something",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "Example 1",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "読",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "よ"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "む"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "読",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "よ"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "まない"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  " (not read)  The む is turned into a ま."
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not hear, Not listen (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "聞かない",
            "kana": "きかない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "きく",
                " -> ",
                "き",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "く"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "か",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not swim (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "泳ぐがない",
            "kana": "およがない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "およぐ",
                " -> ",
                "およ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "ぐ"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "が",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not play (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "遊ぶばない",
            "kana": "あそばない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "あそぶ",
                " -> ",
                "あそ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "ぶ"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "ば",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not drink (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "飲まない",
            "kana": "のまない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "のむ",
                " -> ",
                "の",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "む"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "ま",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not buy (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "買わない",
            "kana": "かわない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "かう",
                " -> ",
                "か",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "う"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "わ",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not read (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "読まない",
            "kana": "よまない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a う verb, we grab the last character and convert it to an あ sound and add a ない. ",
                "よむ",
                " -> ",
                "よ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "む"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                "ま",
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an る Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ない",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an る Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "Remove the last character of the verb and add ない. This changes the verb to mean to \"not\" do something.",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "Example 1",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": "Example 1",
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "見",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "み"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "る"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "見",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "み"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "ない"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  " The る is removed and a ない is added."
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not eat (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "食べない",
            "kana": "たべない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "たべる",
                " -> ",
                "たべ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not sleep (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "寝ない",
            "kana": "ねない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "ねる",
                " -> ",
                "ね",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not see (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "見ない",
            "kana": "みない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "みる",
                " -> ",
                "み",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not consider (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "考えない",
            "kana": "かんがえない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "かんがえる",
                " -> ",
                "かんがえ",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not wake up (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "起きない",
            "kana": "おきない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "おきる",
                " -> ",
                "おき",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not leave, Not come out (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "出ない",
            "kana": "でない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "でる",
                " -> ",
                "で",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not borrow, Not rent (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "借りない",
            "kana": "かりない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": {
            "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
            "type": "span",
            "key": null,
            "ref": null,
            "props": {
              "children": [
                "Since this is a る verb, we just remove the る and add a ない. ",
                "かりる",
                " -> ",
                "かり",
                {
                  "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                  "type": "span",
                  "key": null,
                  "ref": null,
                  "props": {
                    "style": {
                      "textDecoration": "line-through"
                    },
                    "children": "る"
                  },
                  "_owner": null,
                  "_store": {}
                },
                " + ない"
              ]
            },
            "_owner": null,
            "_store": {}
          }
        }
      ]
    },
    "Converting an Irregular Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)-文法": {
      "conceptType": "Conjugation",
      "conjugationType": "ない",
      "Learning": {
        "concept": "Converting an Irregular Verb to Casual Present Negative Tense (ない Form)",
        "explanationHeader": "Meaning",
        "explanation": "There is no pattern, you just memorize the 2 rules in the below examples. This changes the verb to mean to \"not\" do something",
        "extraInfoList": [
          {
            "header": "First Verb",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": null,
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": "する -> しない"
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          },
          {
            "header": "Second Verb",
            "explanation": {
              "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
              "type": "span",
              "key": null,
              "ref": null,
              "props": {
                "children": [
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "来",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "く"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "る"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  },
                  "->",
                  {
                    "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                    "type": "ruby",
                    "key": null,
                    "ref": null,
                    "props": {
                      "children": [
                        "来",
                        {
                          "$$typeof": "$$Symbol:react.element",
                          "type": "rt",
                          "key": null,
                          "ref": null,
                          "props": {
                            "children": "こ"
                          },
                          "_owner": null,
                          "_store": {}
                        },
                        "ない"
                      ]
                    },
                    "_owner": null,
                    "_store": {}
                  }
                ]
              },
              "_owner": null,
              "_store": {}
            }
          }
        ]
      },
      "Questions": [
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not do (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "しない",
            "kana": "しない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "Since this is a irregular verb, we can just memorize \n    the fact that the ない form of する is しない"
        },
        {
          "questionPrompt": "Convert the word to the proper conjugation",
          "question": "Not come (casual)",
          "answer": {
            "kanji": "来ない",
            "kana": "こない"
          },
          "explanationIfUserGetsIncorrect": "Since this is a irregular verb, we can just memorize \n    the fact that the ない form of くる is こない"
        }
      ]
    }
  }
  